Oh, hey.
How was
your audition?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
What are
you doing?
I'm just practicing
blowing you off
'cause I'm going to be
a big movie star.
Oh! You got it?
No, not yet, but the audition
went really good.
What was it for?
Oh, it's this
big-budget period movie
about these three
Italian brothers
who come to America
around the turn of the century.
It's really classy.
Oh, and the director
is supposed to be
the next next Martin Scorsese.
The next next?
Yeah, there's this guy
from Chicago
who's supposed to be the next
Martin Scorsese, right?
But then this guy
is right after him.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Joey, it's Estelle.
I just talked
to the casting people.
They loved you.
They loved me.
Yeah, and they want
to see you again tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
There's just one thing.
Do you have a problem
with full-frontal nudity?
Are you kidding me?
I never rent a movie without it.
Oh.
Uh, okay, uh,
let me call you back.
What's the matter?
They want me to be
totally naked in the movie.
Wow.
I know.
My grandmother's
going to see this.
Grandma's going to have
to get in line.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, the wedding
is so close.
Are you
getting nervous?
Yeah...
but a part of me also can't
wait till it's over.
Chandler and I have this pact
not to have sex again
until the wedding.
A "no sex" pact, huh?
I actually have
one of those going on
with every woman in America.
Hey, Phoebe,
will you give me a hand?
Sure.
I've got to make up
the guest bedroom.
Hey, Cousin Cassie's coming
to stay with us for a few days.
Cassie?
Mm-hmm.
I haven't seen her
in, like, forever.
I wonder if she still carries
that Barbie everywhere she goes.
Ross, she's 25 years old.
So what? I still ha--
No, you're probably right.
Hi.
Hey.
Hey, Pheebs.
Can I talk to you
over here for a second?
Yeah.
Subtle, guys.
What?
I know you're planning
my surprise bridal shower.
Okay, well,
don't ruin it.
Just play along,
at least.
Okay. Sorry.
Oh, my God, we have
to throw her a shower?
Hey.
What'd you decide to do
about the movie?
I don't know, I mean...
it's not like
it's porn.
This is a serious,
legitimate movie, you know?
And the nudity is really
important to the story.
That's what you say about porn.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe I shouldn't even
go on the callback.
No. No, you should.
A lot of major actors
do nude scenes.
And the chance to star
in a movie? Come on.
Well, that's true.
And I am only naked
in one scene.
Plus it sounds really great.
My character's Catholic
and he falls in love
with this Jewish girl.
We run away together and get
caught in this big rainstorm
so we go into this barn
and we undress each other
and hold each other.
It's really sweet and tender.
Plus, everyone's
going to see your thing.
( laughing )
So when can we
have this shower?
She has got so
much going on
we have, we have
only two options.
We have Friday...
Well, that's just
two days away.
What is the
other option?
Yesterday.
If we make it yesterday,
whoo-hoo, we're done.
My God, Phoebe
this is impossible.
We can't do this by Friday.
We have to find a place
we have to invite people
we have to get food--
There's just too much to do.
It's impossible.
We cannot do it.
Calm down!
Okay.
I'm sorry. You're right.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Just calm down, woman!
Phoebe, I already,
I already did.
Oh, okay, then I need
to calm down a little.
Okay.
Okay, I think
we can do this
if we just get
organized, all right?
We have two days
to plan this party.
We just need to make
fast decisions.
Okay!
Okay.
Where are we
going to have it?
Here.
What time? 4:00.
Food--
Finger sandwiches and tea.
Whoo! Great! Very Monica.
And chili.
Ah, you went one too far.
Uh, flowers or balloons?
Both.
We're paying for this.
Neither.
Okay. Um... what shall
we do for the theme?
Lusts of the flesh.
What?
I don't know. Cowboy theme?
( door opening )
Hey.
You know, I'm...
I'm really glad
we decided not to sleep
together before the wedding.
Oh, boy. Me, too.
But, you know, I was thinking,
if we had a big fight
and we broke up
for a few hours
Yeah.
Technically...
we could have sex again.
What do you think,
bossy and domineering?
The wedding is off,
sloppy and immature.
That's me. Come on.
Oh, wait. We can't.
My cousin Cassie's
in the guest room.
We're supposed
to have lunch.
Well, get rid of her,
obsessive and shrill.
Shrill?
The wedding is back on.
I thought I heard voices.
You must be Chandler.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
So, you ready to go?
Yeah.
BARRY WHITE:
♪ It feels so good ♪
♪ You lying here next to me. ♪
Chandler?!
He'll be right with you.
Cassie needs to stay
at your place.
W-Why?
Because Pervy Perverson
over here
can't stop
staring at her.
What?!
Chandler, she's our cousin.
I was not staring
at her, okay?
I was just
listening intently.
It's called being a good
conversationalist. Watch.
Say something.
You were staring about
eight inches south of there.
Fine. She can stay at my place.
By the way, what does Cassie
even look like now?
She looks exactly
like Aunt Marilyn.
Hmm.
So this Aunt Marilyn.
I-is she coming
to the wedding?
Wafer-thin ice.
Hey. I'm back.
Hi, Joey.
Uh, so...
will I be reading
the same scene again?
Actually,
I tried to call you.
You didn't need
to come down here today.
Oh, great.
You know,
I would have been perfect
for this part, but whatever.
You know, thanks for making
a bad decision
and ruining your movie.
Good day.
Wait, Joey.
You didn't need to come down
because the director
saw your tape
from yesterday and loved it.
And... scene.
Huh?
Wasn't that fun?
We did a little improv there.
Yeah. Okay.
So, y-you were saying?
The director thinks
you're really right for the part
and wants to meet you tomorrow.
Wow. Sure. That's great.
Oh, and your agent said
you're okay with the nudity.
Yeah. Yeah, sure, just as long
as it's handled tastefully
and that barn
is not too cold, you know.
Terrific. Well, uh,
there's one more thing.
Uh... Um...
It's really important
to the director
that everything
in this movie is authentic
you know
and so...
in your love scene with Sarah
she talks about how she's
never seen a naked man
who wasn't Jewish.
So...
So... what?
So, uh, well,
the director is insisting
that whoever played that part
be authentically
uh... anatomically...
not Jewish.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes.
Okay.
No. What?
An Italian Catholic immigrant
at this time would not be...
Bar Mitzvahed?
So, to get this part,
you can't be...?
No.
But you are?
Yeah.
But you told them
you weren't.
That's right.
Wow. Wow.
And it's
definitely all gone?
There's nothing there
to work with?
Then what
were you thinking?
I don't know.
I really want this
part, you know?
And they tell you
no matter what
you get asked
during an audition,
you say yes.
Like, if they want
you to ride a horse
you tell them you can
and you just figure out
how to do it later.
Joey, this is not like
learning to ride a horse.
This is like learning
to grow a turtleneck.
I know, I know. Okay?
And apparently,
tomorrow
when I go in to
meet the director
I have to take
off my clothes
so that they can see
what my body looks like.
Oh, my God,
what are you going to do?
I just have to call my agent and
tell her I can't do the part.
( sighs )
Unless...
Unless what?
Well, this may
sound crazy, but...
there may be something
that we could fashion.
Like what?
Well, I'm not sure yet
but, um... off the top
of my head, I'm thinking...
double-sided tape
and some sort of luncheon meat.
Hey.
I've got a great idea.
For party favors
for the shower.
Okay, we get some
mahogany boxes
and carve everyone's
names in them
and then inside
is each person's
individual birthstone.
Okay.
All right,
you take care of that...
Okay.
And...
Meanwhile, the party is tomorrow
and we still
don't have a guest list.
Okay, okay, well, okay, who
do we know that's coming?
Me... Are you?
Hey.
Hey. What's up, Mon?
I'm trying to make
something for Joey.
Mind if I
raid your fridge?
Have at it.
All right... turkey.
That won't work.
Cheese. That won't work.
Olive loaf?!
I hope that won't work.
Are you making him a sandwich?
No, it's more like a wrap.
Okay, so, uh...
I'm going to go, guys
so you can get back to...
deciding on what to get me
for a present.
We have to get her a present?
Okay, but look.
♪ Look at what I got. ♪
It's her address book.
We have a guest list. Ah.
Oh, my God, you're amazing.
Did you just pull that
out of her purse?
Uh-huh. And, a little
seed money for the party.
Oh, nice... Nice.
( loud knocking )
Cassie?
Hey, Ross.
Hi.
It's been so long.
Last time I saw you
you were setting up
your tent in line
to see Return of the Jedi.
( stuttering )
So you did see me that day
because it seemed
like you didn't.
( nervous laughter )
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Come on in.
Thanks for letting
me stay here.
I mean, Monica's place was nice
but her fiancé
sure stares a lot.
Ah...
BARRY WHITE:
♪ It feels so good ♪
♪ You lying here next to me. ♪
Oh, my God.
You do a great Chandler.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I-I have a knack
for impressions.
Well, maybe
after we get reacquainted
uh, you could do me.
Yeah... No!
Cassie...
how you...
how you doing on that...
hot dog?
I'm all done.
Thank God.
I guess the last time
we really hung out
was when our parents
rented that beach house
together.
Oh, right, right...
Oh, remember the time I, uh, I
pinned you down and tickled you
until you cried?
We're probably too old
to do that now.
I'll always remember that summer
because it's when I got
all these freckles.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
And-and...
I'll always remember that summer
because that's when
I realized that we are related.
It took you that long
to figure it out, huh?
Um... I'm a little slow.
Just as our children would be.
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
Hi, thanks for coming.
Thank you.
No? All right.
Oh, so nice to see you.
Do you want-- Okay.
Hey, Rach.
Yeah?
Who the hell are
all these people?
Well, I don't know.
I called all the people
in Monica's phone book
and these are the only ones
that could show up
on 24 hours notice.
Huh.
You know, there's
another word
for people like that.
Losers.
Hi. I'm Rachel.
This is Phoebe.
I'm the Maid of Honor.
How do you know Monica?
I was her accountant
four years ago.
Oh.
Mmm.
I'm very interested
to find out
who's been doing her taxes
the last four years.
That's great.
So, what time is Monica
supposed to get here?
I don't know.
Excuse us for sec.
You didn't tell her
to come?
You were supposed
to tell her.
No, I wasn't.
You were supposed
to tell her.
I was supposed
to bring the cake.
Fine. I'll go call her.
Yes, and please tell her
to bring a cake.
Okay, we have
a lot of options here.
A number of prototypes
for you to try on.
Wow, those look great.
Yeah.
Okay, this one's
a mushroom cap.
Uh, this one is
made of bologna.
And-and the toothpicks?
Oh, just until
the glue dries.
Thank God.
Now these are
more realistic,
but perishable.
Oh.
Okay?
Over here, we have
pink suede, which is nice
but, um, if it gets wet
then, you know, it's
going to shrink.
Yeah, maybe we just
take that one away.
I also did a little
something in fur
but, um, that's
really just for me.
Okay, um...
So why don't you
go into your room
and try these on
and we'll see--
we'll get a better idea
of what's going to work.
Thanks.
You are such a good friend
and this is so weird.
Ow!
Toothpick?
Yeah.
What are you trying on now?
The fruit roll-up.
And?
Delicious.
Joey...
Wait a minute.
We have a winner.
What? Which one?
The Silly Putty.
Not so silly anymore.
She's your cousin.
If she knew what was
going on in your head
she'd think
you were sick.
Or would she?
Let's back up for a second.
She was the one who suggested
opening a bottle of wine.
She was the one
who turned down the lights.
that wanted to rent
Logan's Run,
the sexiest movie ever.
Oh, I know that look.
Forget it. I want it.
She wants it.
I'm going in.
( gasps )
What the hell
are you doing?
Say something clever.
Okay, doesn't
have to be clever.
Just has to be words.
Say some words.
Any words will do.
Oh, my God.
This is the longest that anyone
has not... talked... ever.
There is nothing you could say
to make this worse
so just say something!
I-I-I haven't had sex
in a very long time.
Yeah, you really shouldn't have
said anything.
Phoebe, Rachel... it's Monica.
I wonder what you could possibly
need me for
in such short notice.
Oh.
Oh, Monica, we
are so sorry.
For what?
Well, first, for forgetting
to throw you a bridal shower.
And then, for forgetting
to invite you to it.
You already had it?
Yeah, well, we called
everyone in your phone book
and a bunch of people came
but it took us so long
to get you here
that they had to leave.
RACHEL:
Yeah, we wanted
to throw you
a big surprise
and a great shower
and... and now you
don't have either.
We ruined everything.
Well, no, wait a minute.
That's not true.
No, what you did,
that was really sweet.
And it kind of works out
for the best.
What do you mean?
Well, now I get to spend
my shower
with the only people
I really love.
I mean, I get all those presents
without having to talk
to a bunch of people
I don't even like.
S-surprise.
Surprise, Monica.
And what's cool is,
the character
is from Naples, right?
Yeah.
My whole family's from Naples.
Oh, that's great.
Okay, well, I've heard
everything I need to hear...
we just need to,
uh... Leslie?
Uh, Joey, this is
the awkward part.
Oh, hey, right.
Not a problem.
I totally understand.
You need to, you know
make sure I don't have any
horrible scars or tattoos.
Don't you worry
I have nothing to hide.
So, there you go.
That's me.
100% natural.
( putty bounces and rolls )
I tell you that has never
happened before.
Cassie, are you finding
everything okay in there?
Yeah. Thank you
so much
for letting me
stay here.
Oh, it's no problem.
I've...
BARRY WHITE:
♪ It feels so good ♪
♪ You lying here next to me ♪
♪ Oh, what a groove... ♪
( music stops )
What?
Say something.
Say anything.
Ask her out,
she's not your cousin.